Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Photography and Photographic Formats
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Processing Material, circa 1875-circa 1993; Series III; 7.3; (13 boxes)
  - Photographic Processing Material
    - Technifinish Laboratories, Rochester, New York, Film interleaving paper, circa 1940 (Box 51, Folder 427)
    - Frederick D. Fisher, Embossa No. 2, circa 1950 (Box 52, Folder 428-429)
    - Frederick D. Fisher, Embossa No. 3, circa 1950 (Box 52, Folder 430)
  - Printing Masks
    Arranged alphabetically by manufacturer followed by masks made by unidentified firms.
    Printing masks are opaque sheets with openings or transparencies that allow light to shine through in a defined pattern, which photographic processors use when printing photographs to impart particular shapes or effect on the printed image.
    - Eastman Kodak, Rochester, New York (Box 52, Folder 431)
    - George E. Millard, Manning's Masks, Chicago, Illinois, circa 1900 (Box 52, Folder 432)
    - Millard and Manning, M&M Photo Matts, Chicago, Illinois (Box 52, Folder 433-434)
    - Spurr's Scroll and Border Negatives, Creston, Iowa, circa 1891 (Box 52, Folder 435)
    - Unidentified manufacturer, Paper printing masks (Box 52, Folder 436-439)
    - Unidentified manufacturer, Metal printing masks, circles (Box 52, Folder 440)
    - Unidentified manufacturer, Metal printing masks, ovals (Box 52, Folder 441)
    - Unidentified manufacturer, All-in-one mats (Box 52, Folder 442)
  - Photographic Negatives
    Organized under two headings: Boxes with Unused Negatives and Empty Negative Boxes.
    This subseries includes examples of unused photographic negatives, as well as empty boxes used to hold and market negatives.
    - Boxes with Unused Negatives
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Stanley Dry Plates, circa 1900 (Box 53, Folder 443)
      - Union Photographique Industrielle Lumiere & Jougla, Autochrome plates, 1920 March (Box 53, Folder 444)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Wratten & Wainwright Panchromatic Dry Plates, circa 1930 (Box 53, Folder 445)
    - Empty Negative Boxes
      - M. A. Seed Dry Plate Company, Extra Rapid Dry Plates, circa 1887 (Box 53, Folder 446-448)
      - G. Cramer Dry Plate Company, Cramer's Isochromatic Photo Dry Plates, circa 1891-circa 1920 (Box 53, Folder 449)
      - Close & Cone, or Edward G. Cone Company, Quad Dry Plates, circa 1896-circa 1897 (Box 53, Folder 450)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Eastman's Dry Plates, circa 1896-circa 1897 (Box 54, Folder 451-454)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Stanley Dry Plates, circa 1900 (Box 54, Folder 455)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Seed's Dry Plates, circa 1905 (Box 54, Folder 456)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Standard Dry Plates, circa 1905 (Box 54, Folder 457)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Eastman 40 Plates, circa 1925-circa 1940 (Box 54, Folder 458)
  - Photographic Paper
    Organized under two headings: Photographic Paper Boxes and Photographic Paper Envelopes.
    This subseries includes examples of boxes and envelopes used to hold and market photographic papers, as well as some examples of used paper.
    - Photographic Paper Boxes
      - American Aristotype Company, Blue Label paper, circa 1895 (Box 55, Folder 459)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Solio paper, circa 1898-circa 1899 (Box 55, Folder 460-461)
      - Kilborn Photo Paper Company, Kruxo paper, circa 1910 (Box 55, Folder 462)
      - Canadian Kodak Company, Azo paper, circa 1912 (Box 55, Folder 463)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Velvet Velox paper, circa 1914 (Box 55, Folder 464)
        Includes unused paper
    - Photographic Paper Envelopes
      - New Jersey Aristotype Company, Albuma paper, circa 1899 (Box 56, Folder 465)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Velvet Velox paper, circa 1901 (Box 56, Folder 466)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Solio paper, circa 1901 (Box 56, Folder 467)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Company, Silvered Darko paper, circa 1910 (Box 56, Folder 468)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Velox paper, circa 1914 (Box 56, Folder 469)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Velvet Velox paper, circa 1919 (Box 56, Folder 470)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Azo, Grade E, Hard, paper, circa 1920 (Box 56, Folder 471)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Azo, Grade F, Hard X, paper, circa 1920 (Box 56, Folder 472)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Azo, Grade E, Hard X, paper, circa 1921 (Box 56, Folder 473)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Velvet Velox, double weight, paper, circa 1921 (Box 56, Folder 474)
        Includes an instruction sheet for the paper
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Azo, Grade E, No. 2, paper, circa 1925 (Box 56, Folder 475)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Azo, Grade F, No. 3, paper, circa 1932 (Box 56, Folder 476)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, Glossy Velox, Grade F, No. 2, paper, circa 1939 (Box 56, Folder 477)
    - Unused Paper Loose
      - Ansco, Cyko postcard paper, 1920-1928 (Box 56, Folder 478)
- Photographs by Format, circa 1855-1940; Series IV; 16.6; (57 boxes)
  This series consists of examples of photographic formats collected by Palmquist.
  Series IV is organized into eight subseries: Tintypes and Wet Collodion Processes, Stereograph Cards, Photographic Prints with Hand Coloring, Photographs on Glass, Miniature Photographs and Stanhopes, Photographic Transparencies, Photographic and Crayon Enlargements, and Photographically Illustrated Printed Material.
  - Tintypes and Wet Collodion Processes
    This subseries chiefly consists of tintypes and wet collodion processes, as well as material related to their production.
    Wet collodion processes use a collodion binder on material, which a photographer must coat, expose, and develop before the collodion dries. Wet collodion processes include ambrotypes, melainotypes, and tintypes, although photographers also used the process on cloth and paper.
    Tintypes are a wet collodion process that produces a direct positive image on a thin sheet of lacquered metal, usually iron.
    Tintypes come in many sizes. Manufacturers produced the metal used to produce tintypes and sold it to the photographer or photography studio. The photographer used the full plate to make a large photograph, or usually cut the plate to make multiple smaller photographs. As a result, most tintypes have irregular cuts including crooked edges and clipped corners.
    Organized under ten headings: Wet Collodion Processes on Cloth and Paper, Melainotypes, Unused Tintype Plates and Sleeves, Tintypes by Identified Photographers, Tintypes with Identified Subjects, Tintypes with Identified Locations, Full Plate Tintypes, Studio Portrait Tintypes, Tintypes of Exteriors, Tintype Copy Photographs, and Gem Photographs
    - Wet Collodion Processes on Cloth and Paper
      - Barnes, George W., Rockford, Illinois, Wet collodion process photograph on cloth and mounted on a carte de visite (Box 57, Folder 479)
      - Unidentified photographers, Wet plate process studio portraits on card stock and paper (Box 57, Folder 480)
    - Melainotypes (Box 57, Folder 481)
      Melainotypes are a very early form of tintype.
      In 1854, Hamilton Lanphere Smith (1819-1903, Yale 1839), a chemistry professor at Kenyon College, developed the Melainotype process. Smith sold the patent rights to Peter Neff, Jr., one of his students, who patented the process in 1856.
    - Unused Tintype Plates and Sleeves
      - Ninth plate (Box 57, Folder 482)
      - Quarter plate (Box 57, Folder 483)
      - Half plate (Box 57, Folder 484)
      - Paper Sleeves (Box 57, Folder 485-494)
    - Tintypes by Identified Photographers
      - Connecticut
        - Kellogg, E. P.; Hartford (Box 58, Folder 495)
        - Morgan & Kenyon; New London (Box 58, Folder 496)
        - Morgan, N. D.; Norwich (Box 58, Folder 497)
      - Illinois
        - Cadman; Jacksonville (Box 58, Folder 498)
        - Harris, C. H.; New Windsor (Box 58, Folder 499)
        - Lockhard, William R.; Marshall (Box 58, Folder 500)
        - Reed, Oscar O.; Paris (Box 58, Folder 501)
        - Tandy; Jacksonville (Box 58, Folder 502)
        - Tate, L. F.; Oneida (Box 58, Folder 503)
        - Tull, B. H.; Lena (Box 58, Folder 504)
        - Warner; Quincy (Box 58, Folder 505)
      - Indiana
        - Judkin; Indianapolis (Box 58, Folder 506)
      - Maine
        - Collins; Portland (Box 58, Folder 507)
        - Robinson; Oakland (Box 58, Folder 508)
        - Ross, W. J.; Machias (Box 58, Folder 509)
        - Sawyer, S. W.; Bangor (Box 58, Folder 510)
        - Vose; Machias (Box 58, Folder 511)
        - Wormell, Elestus S.; Portland (Box 58, Folder 512)
      - Maryland
        - McLaughlin; Cumberland (Box 58, Folder 513)
        - Pope, J. H.; Baltimore (Box 58, Folder 514)
        - Trainor, M. D.; Marshall Hall (Box 58, Folder 515)
      - Massachusetts
        - Boston Tent Gallery (Box 58, Folder 516)
        - Clark, E. H.; Great Barrington (Box 58, Folder 517)
        - Crane, G. G.; Taunton (Box 58, Folder 518)
        - Dodge, George K.; Boston (Box 58, Folder 519)
        - Gillmore; Worcester (Box 58, Folder 520)
        - Lamb, C. F.; Southbridge (Box 58, Folder 521)
        - Mitchell, J. S.; Boston (Box 58, Folder 522)
        - Strathmore; Crescent Beach (Box 58, Folder 523)
      - Michigan
        - Simonds; Detroit (Box 58, Folder 524)
      - Missouri
        - Atkinson, Charles W.; Kansas City (Box 58, Folder 525)
        - Manning, A. W.; Edina (Box 58, Folder 526)
      - New Hampshire
        - Batchelder, J. C.; Nashua (Box 58, Folder 527)
        - Clark; Sanbornton (Box 58, Folder 528)
        - Clark, S. A.; Laconia (Box 58, Folder 529)
        - Stark, A. D.; Manchester (Box 58, Folder 530)
      - New Jersey
        - Smith, J. Rennie; Asbury Park (Box 58, Folder 531)
      - New York (Box 58, Folder 532)
        - Abbott; Oneida (Box 58, Folder 533)
        - Beals, H. C.; Fulton (Box 58, Folder 534)
        - Cary, C. H.; New York City (Box 58, Folder 535)
        - Cheapest Gallery in the World, Brooklyn (Box 58, Folder 536)
        - Gilbert, E.; Olcott Beach (Box 58, Folder 537)
        - Godfrey, George W. (Box 58, Folder 538)
        - Heney; New York City (Box 58, Folder 539)
        - Hennigar; New York City (Box 58, Folder 540)
        - Jones; Coney Island (Box 58, Folder 541)
        - Jordan Brothers; Seneca Falls and Utica (Box 58, Folder 542)
        - Law, J.; Utica (Box 58, Folder 543)
        - Le Roy; Newburgh (Box 58, Folder 544)
        - Russell, Frank; New York City (Box 58, Folder 545)
        - Sherwood; New York City (Box 58, Folder 546)
        - Sherwood; Peekskill (Box 58, Folder 547)
        - Stevens, George W.; Sacandaga Park (Box 58, Folder 548)
        - Wasson; Brooklyn (Box 58, Folder 549)
      - Pennsylvania
        - Bruce & Fisher; Bloody Run and Everett (Box 58, Folder 550)
        - Foedisch, Charles; Honesdale (Box 58, Folder 551)
        - Gilbert, C. M.; Philadelphia (Box 58, Folder 552)
        - Green; Johnstown (Box 58, Folder 553)
        - Hildreth, D. L.; Philadelphia (Box 59)
          Full plate "pennellograph," a hand-colored tintype, of a postmortem portrait of an infant
        - Lothrop; Philadelphia (Box 58, Folder 554)
        - Momeyer, W. P.; McKeesport (Box 58, Folder 555)
        - Trasks; Philadelphia (Box 58, Folder 556)
        - Truxell, J. H.; Philadelphia (Box 58, Folder 557)
        - Wager, S. D.; Erie (Box 58, Folder 558)
      - Rhode Island
        - Alden, A. E.; Providence (Box 58, Folder 559)
        - Merigold; Crescent Park (Box 58, Folder 560)
      - Vermont
        - Continental Ferrotype Company; Burlington (Box 58, Folder 561)
      - Virginia
        - Campbell, C.; Petersburg (Box 58, Folder 562)
        - Minnis, G. W.; Richmond (Box 58, Folder 563)
      - Washington, D. C.
        - Cole, D. H.; Washington (Box 58, Folder 564)
      - Washington
        - Judkins, J. C. (Box 58, Folder 565)
      - West Virginia
        - Flynn & Cummings; Harper's Ferry (Box 58, Folder 566)
      - Wisconsin
        - Beverage, M. C.; Oconto (Box 58, Folder 567)
        - Bishop, Frank, Jr.; Milwaukee (Box 58, Folder 568)
          Tintype with a double exposure portrait of the same man
      - Travelling Photographers
        - Douglass (Box 58, Folder 569)
        - Mapel, Emri (Box 58, Folder 570)
        - Mason & Thompson (Box 58, Folder 571)
        - Pearce, W. H. (Box 58, Folder 572)
        - Williams, C. C. (Box 58, Folder 573)
      - Photographers Outside the United States
        - Canada
          - Trenham, N. J.; Arnprior, Ontario (Box 58, Folder 574)
          - Tuck, J. P.; Fredericton, New Brunswick (Box 58, Folder 575)
          - Wallis, J. D.; Ottawa, Ontario (Box 58, Folder 576)
        - England (Box 58, Folder 577)
          - Jewell, J.; Liverpool and Manchester (Box 58, Folder 578)
          - Kruger, S. D.; Birkenhead and Liverpool (Box 58, Folder 579)
          - Lovell, A. J.; Whitehaven (Box 58, Folder 580)
        - Unidentified Locations
          - Harvey (Box 58, Folder 581)
          - Purden (Box 58, Folder 582)
          - Steven, B. F. (Box 58, Folder 583)
    - Tintypes with Identified Subjects
      - Addison, Rosie, and Maggie Jones (Box 60, Folder 584)
      - Ames, Mary Otis (Box 60, Folder 585)
      - Bailey, Susie (Box 60, Folder 586)
      - Boyle, Charles (Box 60, Folder 587)
      - Bradshaw, M. (Box 60, Folder 588)
      - Brown, Callie (Box 60, Folder 589)
      - Colvin, W. T. (Box 60, Folder 590)
      - Crawford, George W., and Henry (Box 60, Folder 591)
      - Cross, Minna (Box 60, Folder 592)
      - Dever, Mattie Douk (Box 60, Folder 593)
      - Emery, George, and E. L. (Box 60, Folder 594)
      - Finley, Mr. and Mrs. (Box 60, Folder 595)
      - Frost, Edith (Box 60, Folder 596)
      - Garwood, Thomas, and Susan (Box 60, Folder 597)
      - Gloss, H. R. (Box 60, Folder 598)
      - Graber, W. K., Professor, and daughter, Minnie Michel (Box 60, Folder 599)
      - Grove, S. H. (Box 60, Folder 600)
      - Gwein, Rolland (Box 60, Folder 601)
      - Hall, Robert F. (Box 60, Folder 602)
      - Hanna, James W. (Box 60, Folder 603)
      - Hayden, Charles (Box 60, Folder 604)
      - James, J. W. (Box 60, Folder 605)
      - Johnson, Almina (Box 60, Folder 606)
      - Johnson, Fannie (Box 60, Folder 607)
      - Johnson, Plum Obeira (Box 60, Folder 608)
      - Johnson, Wiard (Box 60, Folder 609)
      - Jones, Darsy? (Box 60, Folder 610)
      - Keller, Ralph Olmstead (Box 60, Folder 611)
      - Kirby, Claire (died October 1880) (Box 60, Folder 612)
      - McKillan, George (Box 60, Folder 613)
      - Miller (Box 60, Folder 614)
      - Mitschler, Lela Davey, 1888 March (Box 61)
        Tintype in a frame
      - Mudgette, Bernie (Box 60, Folder 615)
      - Myers, G. D. (Box 60, Folder 616)
      - Olson, Hulda (Box 60, Folder 617)
      - Pickard, N. (Box 60, Folder 618)
      - Price, S. C. (Box 60, Folder 619)
      - Rager, Lizzie (Box 60, Folder 620)
      - Richardson (Box 60, Folder 621)
        Copy photograph of a man from a studio portrait originally made by Carleton E. Watkins
      - Richardson, Eliza Knight (Box 60, Folder 622)
      - Shores, Amasa (Box 60, Folder 623)
      - Smith, Emma Lettice, and Hattie Estelle (Box 60, Folder 624)
      - Stone, Abbie (Box 60, Folder 625)
      - Strong (Box 60, Folder 626)
      - Stunning, T.M. (Box 60, Folder 627)
      - Sturtevant, Willie (Box 60, Folder 628)
      - Ten Eyck, Carrie, Lizzie, and Winnie (Box 60, Folder 629)
      - Tucks, James (Box 60, Folder 630)
      - Turner, Annie Christina (1875-1931), and Augusta Smith (Box 60, Folder 631)
      - Turner, Maud (Box 60, Folder 632)
      - Turner, Meda (Box 60, Folder 633)
      - Turner, William Price (1862-1931) (Box 60, Folder 634)
      - Ward, Benjamin (Box 60, Folder 635)
      - Wellman, Adaline F. (Box 60, Folder 636)
      - Wheeler, Emily, and Mary (Box 60, Folder 637)
      - Woodall, Dana (Box 60, Folder 638)
      - Group (Identified) (Box 60, Folder 639)
      - Group (Identified) (Box 60, Folder 640)
    - Tintypes with Identified Locations
      - Eureka, California (Box 60, Folder 641)
      - Group at the Golden Gate International Exposition, San Francisco, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 642)
      - Group at Greenwich, Connecticut, 1884 (Box 60, Folder 643)
      - Lewis and Clark Centennial Exposition, Portland, Oregon, 1905 (Box 60, Folder 644)
      - Mounted men at 7th Avenue and 116th Street, New York City (Box 60, Folder 645)
      - Rockaway Beach, Queens, New York, 1901 July 21 (Box 60, Folder 646)
      - Mission San Gabriel Arcángel, San Gabriel, California, 1931 February 8 (Box 60, Folder 647)
      - Cliff House, San Francisco (Box 60, Folder 648)
      - Niagara Falls (Box 60, Folder 649)
    - Full Plate Tintypes
      This component consists of full plate tintypes, usually measuring around 8.5 by 6.5 inches.
      Organized under five headings: Studio Portraits with a Single Figure, Studio Portraits with Two Figures, Studio Portraits of a Group, Exteriors, and Copy Photographs of Studio Portraits.
      - Studio Portraits with a Single Figure
        - Girl posed standing, full-length figure (Box 62, Folder 650)
        - Girl posed sitting, full-length figure (Box 62, Folder 651)
        - Girl posed sitting, half figure (Box 62, Folder 652)
        - Boy posed standing, full-length figure (Box 63)
          Full plate tintype in a frame
        - Woman posed sitting, bust figures (Box 62, Folder 653-657)
        - Woman posed sitting, half figures (Box 62, Folder 658-662)
        - Woman posed standing, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 663-664)
        - Man posed sitting, bust figures (Box 62, Folder 665-671)
        - Man posed sitting, half figures (Box 62, Folder 672-677)
        - Man posed sitting, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 678-682)
        - Man posed standing, full-length figure (Box 62, Folder 683)
      - Studio Portraits with Two Figures
        - Boy posed sitting, full-length figure, with a dog (Box 62, Folder 684)
        - Two girls posed sitting, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 685)
        - Girl and boy posed sitting, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 686)
        - Child and woman posed sitting, half figures (Box 62, Folder 687)
        - Two women posed sitting, bust figures (Box 62, Folder 688)
        - Woman posed sitting and a man posed sitting, half figures (Box 62, Folder 689)
        - Woman posed standing and a man posed sitting, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 690)
        - Man and woman posed sitting, half figures (Box 62, Folder 691)
        - Two men sitting, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 692)
      - Studio Portraits of a Group
        - Woman posed sitting and holding an infant, and a man posed standing, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 693)
        - Two women posed sitting, one holding a photograph, and a woman posed standing, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 694)
        - Woman and man posed sitting, each holding a girl, with a girl posed standing and a girl posed sitting, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 695)
        - Woman and man posed sitting, and a boy and man posed standing, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 696)
        - Woman and man posed sitting, and a boy and two men posed standing, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 697)
        - Two women and three men posed standing and wearing eighteenth-century-style clothing, full-length figures (Box 62, Folder 698)
        - Twelve girls posed sitting and standing, full-length figures; the window of the photographer's studio visible in the frame (Box 62, Folder 699)
      - Exteriors
        - View of a light-colored house with a windmill, and two women posed sitting and standing on the porch and a man in a horse-drawn buggy (Box 62, Folder 700)
        - View of a storefront with a sign, "Henderson's," and a group of five men and four women posed standing, as well as a man on its roof, and man and boy in a horse-drawn buggy (Box 62, Folder 701)
      - Copy Photographs of Studio Portraits
        - Girl posed sitting, bust figure (Box 62, Folder 702)
        - Woman posed sitting with a child, bust figures (Box 62, Folder 703)
        - Woman posed sitting, bust figure (Box 62, Folder 704-705)
        - Woman posed sitting, bust figure, circa 1875 (Box 64)
          Tintype enlargement, larger than a full plate, in a period mat
        - Woman posed sitting, half figure (Box 62, Folder 706)
        - Man posed sitting, bust figure (Box 62, Folder 707-708)
        - Woman posed standing, full-length figure (Box 62, Folder 709)
    - Studio Portrait Tintypes
      Organized under fifteen headings: Studio Portraits of Dogs, Studio Portraits of Figures in Costume, Studio Portraits of Figures in Action, Studio Portraits of Figures with Props, Studio Portraits of Figures at Tourist Sites, Tintype Stereographs, Studio Portraits of Infants, Studio Portraits of Girls, Studio Portraits of Boys, Studio Portraits of Children, Studio Portraits of Children and Adults, Studio Portraits of Women, Studio Portraits of Men, Studio Portraits of Men and Women, and Studio Portraits of Postmortems.
      This component consists of tintypes of studio portraits with dimensions less than 8.5 by 6.5 inches.
      - Studio Portraits of Dogs
        - Dog Alone (Box 65, Folder 710)
        - Dog with single figure (Box 65, Folder 711)
        - Dog with two figures (Box 65, Folder 712)
        - Dog with three figures (Box 65, Folder 713)
      - Studio Portraits of Figures in Costume
        - Women in costume (Box 65, Folder 714)
        - Men in costume (Box 65, Folder 715)
        - Men in fraternal costume (Box 65, Folder 716)
        - Men and women in costume (Box 65, Folder 717)
        - Women wearing occupational costume and with tools (Box 65, Folder 718)
        - Men wearing occupational costume and with tools (Box 65, Folder 719)
        - Women and girls with long hair (Box 65, Folder 720)
      - Studio Portraits of Figures in Action
        - Reading (Box 65, Folder 721)
        - Writing (Box 65, Folder 722)
        - Drinking (Box 65, Folder 723)
        - Playing table games (Box 65, Folder 724)
        - Boxing (Box 65, Folder 725)
        - Smoking (Box 65, Folder 726)
      - Studio Portraits of Figures with Props
        Props are movable physical objects used in a photographer's studio, such as furnishings, decorations, and objects held by the figures.
        - Automobiles (Box 65, Folder 727)
        - Bicycles (Box 65, Folder 728)
        - Boats (Box 65, Folder 729)
        - Equine (Box 65, Folder 730)
        - Firearms (Box 65, Folder 731)
        - Fishing poles and fish (Box 65, Folder 732)
        - Moon (Box 65, Folder 733)
        - Musical instruments (Box 65, Folder 734)
        - Ostrich (Box 65, Folder 735)
        - Photographs (Box 65, Folder 736)
        - Still life (Box 65, Folder 737)
      - Studio Portraits of Figures at Tourist Sites
        - Bathing suits (Box 65, Folder 738)
        - Cut-out portraits (Box 65, Folder 739)
        - Patriotic (Box 65, Folder 740)
        - Water flume (Box 65, Folder 741)
      - Tintype Stereographs (Box 65, Folder 742)
      - Studio Portraits of Infants
        - Infant with an obscured adult (Box 66, Folder 743)
        - Infant (Box 66, Folder 744)
        - Two infants (Box 66, Folder 745)
        - Infant and child (Box 66, Folder 746)
      - Studio Portraits of Girls
        - Girl posed sitting, full-length figure (Box 67, Folder 747)
        - Girl posed sitting, half figure (Box 67, Folder 748)
        - Girl posed sitting, bust figure (Box 67, Folder 749)
        - Girl posed standing, full-length figure (Box 67, Folder 750)
        - Girl posed standing, half figure (Box 67, Folder 751)
      - Studio Portraits of Boys
        - Boy posed sitting, full-length figure (Box 68, Folder 752)